tomgreen.com 2009-12-28

# TomGreen.com - The Channel

### TomGreen.com Customer Privacy Policy

The TomGreen.com Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by TomGreen.com anytime you interact with TomGreen.com, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase TomGreen.com products and services, or when you call our sales or support number. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at TomGreen.com, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

### Why we collect personal information

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

If you do not want TomGreen.com to keep you up to date with the latest information on products and services click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email you receive and you will be removed from our email database.

### What information we collect and how we may use it

There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better products. For example:

  * We may ask for your personal information when you’re discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, registering for a seminar, participating in an online survey, registering your products, or purchasing a product.
  * When you interact with TomGreen.com, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the TomGreen.com products you own; and information relating to a support or service issue.
  * We also collect information for market research purposes — such as your occupation and where you use your computer — to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service.
  * We collect information regarding customer activities on our websites, TomGreen.com and Channel747.com. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites, products, and services are of most interest to them.
  * We may use personal information to provide products that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve TomGreen.com products.

If you use a comment forum or chat room on a TomGreen.com website you should be aware that any information you share is visible to other users. Personally identifiable information you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected, or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages. TomGreen.com is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. For example, if you choose to make information, which was previously non-public, available by enabling certain user features, TomGreen.com will collect that information from your interaction and the information will become publicly available.

### When we disclose your information

TomGreen.com takes your privacy very seriously. TomGreen.com does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers.

### Within the TomGreen.com Group

To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within the TomGreen.com group globally who will take steps to safeguard it in accordance with TomGreen.com’s privacy policy.

### With our service providers, vendors, and strategic partners

There are also times when it may be advantageous for TomGreen.com to make certain personal information about you available to companies that TomGreen.com has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for TomGreen.com to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with TomGreen.com’s policies, except if we inform you otherwise at the time of collection. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and content on the TomGreen.com website.

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

### How we protect your personal information

TomGreen.com takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

The TomGreen.com Music Store and Subscription Service uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. To make purchases from the TomGreen.com Music Store and to enroll in the Subscription Service, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Safari, Firefox 2.0 or later, or Internet Explorer 7 or later. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it’s transmitted over the Internet.

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Avoid saving passwords and credit card numbers in your browser cache, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Safari.

### Integrity of your personal information

TomGreen.com has safeguards in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. Naturally, you always have the right to access and correct the personal information you have provided. You can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by emailing privacy@tomgreen.com to get a current listing of the contact information we have on file.

### Kids

TomGreen.com recognizes that parents, guardians, or other adults often purchase our products for family use, including use by minors. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 for marketing purposes, but because some information is collected electronically, it can appear to be the personal information of the TomGreen.com purchaser of the product, and will be treated as such by this privacy policy. If a child under 13 submits personal information to TomGreen.com and we learn that that personal information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible.

### Cookies and other technologies

As is standard practice on many corporate websites, TomGreen.com uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We also use cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our products and services, such as the TomGreen.com Music Store, and Subscription Service. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.

Information such as your country and language helps us provide a more useful online experience. And your contact information, and information about your computer helps us provide you with customer service.

If, however, you prefer not to enable cookies, please email privacy@tomgreen.com, and you will be contacted with instructions explaining step-by-step how you can disable cookies. Please note that certain features of the TomGreen.com website will not be available once cookies are disabled.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. TomGreen.com will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

In some of our email messages we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the TomGreen.com website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email.

In addition we use pixel tags — tiny graphic images — to tell us what parts of our website customers have visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches customers perform on our site.

Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read. And they tell us whether emails have been opened to ensure that we’re sending only messages that are of interest to our customers. We store all of this information in a secure database, located in the United States.

### Our companywide commitment to your privacy

As we said, TomGreen.com takes protecting your privacy very seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to TomGreen.com employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company. In addition, TomGreen.com supports industry initiatives, such as TRUSTe, to preserve privacy rights on the Internet and in all aspects of electronic commerce.

### International users

TomGreen.com abides by the safe harbor framework set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information collected from the European Union. The following link provides more information about the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program: <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

TomGreen.com has links to the sites of other companies. TomGreen.com is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

### Privacy questions

If you have questions or concerns about TomGreen.com’s Customer Privacy Policy or data processing, please use the email address below to contact us. The TomGreen.com Privacy Police will respond to your inquiry promptly.

If you do not want TomGreen.com to keep you up to date with the latest information on products and services click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email you received and you will be removed from our email database. Naturally, if you notify us that you do not want us to use your information for a particular purpose, we will not do so.

TomGreen.com may update its privacy policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated privacy policy.

TomGreen.com 1801 Century Park East, Ste. 2160, Los Angeles, CA 90067

_Last updated January 09, 2009_

© 2009 TomGreen.com. All rights reserved.
